So I'm here packing a go-do smart, funny, and black in Nashville, Tennessee, and boom!
Breaking!
The two Tennessee state lawmakers, Justin Jones, Nashville, and Justin J. Pearson, Memphis,
who were expelled from the state legislature earlier this year for their protests of gun
violence, have easily won a special primary election.
Justin Jones ran unopposed.
Justin J. Pearson won 94% of the motherfucking vote.
So, the Tennessee GOP, you know, they thought they was doing things.
They thought they was really, like, running things.
And all they did was run it up.
Ran them up the flagpole to wave over the nation.
Because we all are team Justin and Justin.
And even those of us who ain't even from Tennessee.
Congratulations, brothers.